Hello everyone welcome to my
youtube0 Support and resistance can be formed,
we will know in this video, so
before starting the video, if you have come to our channel for the first
time then do like the video and subscribe to the channel
because I keep finding
such stocks for you daily,
so let's start, let's talk about the
current price of ICICI Lombard stock, at
this time this stock is
seen trending around ₹1 1932,
if the stock makes a lower circuit from its current price,
then our first important support can be
formed around ₹1 40, if the stock
breaks down its first support, then
our second most important support can be
formed around ₹1 73, if the stock
makes an upper circuit from its current price, then our
first important resistance will be ₹2000000